let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Évszakok",
        answer: "B. Estaçoes",
        options: [
                "A. Inverno",
                "B. Estaçoes",
                "C. Nuvem",
                "D. Quente"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Tavasz",
        answer: "A. (a) Primavera",
        options: [
                "A. (a) Primavera",
                "B. (o) Verão",
                "C. (o) Outono",
                "D. (o) Inverno"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Nyár",
        answer: "D. (o) Verão",
        options: [
                "A. (o) Inverno",
                "B. (o) Outono",
                "C. (a) Primavera",
                "D. (o) Verão"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Ősz",
        answer: "A. (o) Outono",
        options: [
                "A. (o) Outono",
                "B. (o) Verão",
                "C. (a) Primavera",
                "D. (o) Inverno"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Tél",
        answer: "A. (o) Inverno",
        options: [
                "A. (o) Inverno",
                "B. (a) Primavera",
                "C. (o) Verão",
                "D. (o) Outono"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Szivárvány",
        answer: "D. Arco-íris",
        options: [
                "A. Nuvem",
                "B. Estaçoes",
                "C. Frio",
                "D. Arco-íris"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Felhő",
        answer: "B. Nuvem",
        options: [
                "A. Céu",
                "B. Nuvem",
                "C. Frio",
                "D. Quente"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Meleg",
        answer: "D. Quente",
        options: [
                "A. Verão",
                "B. Frio",
                "C. Primavera",
                "D. Quente"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Hideg van",
        answer: "A. Está frio",
        options: [
                "A. Está frio",
                "B. Está quente",
                "C. Frio",
                "D. Quente"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Ég",
        answer: "D. Céu",
        options: [
                "A. Nuvem",
                "B. Arco-íris",
                "C. Estaçoes",
                "D. Céu"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Meleg van",
        answer: "D. Está quente",
        options: [
                "A. Está ventando",
                "B. Está frio",
                "C. Está úmido",
                "D. Está quente"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "Hideg",
        answer: "B. Frio",
        options: [
                "A. Outono",
                "B. Frio",
                "C. Céu",
                "D. Inverno"
        ]
    }
];